http://www.paganpresence.com/privacy-policy

For A Limited Time Free Shipping Is Available For Domestic Orders Of $50 Or More.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.Pagan Presence, Inc.HomeShopMoreHomeShopHomeShop
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy Our Commitment to PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any Pagan Presence website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and order a Psychic Reading. The types of personal information collected at these pages are as follows:  Consumer Orders
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
Business Orders
Business Name
Address
Credit/Debit Card Information
Any Information You Give Us To Pass Along To The Medium/Psychic Reader
The Way We Use Information We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We offer gift certificates by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses may be used to provide you with promotional and company information. These addresses are not shared with outside parties.All users have the option on our website to register for our email newsletter, which features products we offer,new product announcements, new services announcements, special event appearance schedule, and information you may find useful. You can opt out of receiving our email newsletter at any time by using the Unsuscribe Link in the newsletter or emailing the Web Master at webmaster@paganpresence.com.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to be used by our sales and marketing departments. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment to Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. How You Can Access or Correct Your Information You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending your request to:
Web Master
Pagan Presence, Inc.
P O Box 803
Medina, OH 44258-0803
Please include your full name, current address, and a daytime phone number. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by logging into your account on our website and updating the information or by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 330-805-1675 or email us at webmaster@paganpresence.com
Copyright © 2018 Pagan Presence, Inc. - All Rights Reserved.Our CustomersPrivacy PolicyShipping PoliciesAbout UsReturns & ExchangesWhole SalePowered by GoDaddy Website Builder
